I won't be home
for the next few days.
Your meeting seems important.
Is there a problem, Mom?
How can I help you if you don't
tell me what the problem is?
He's here.
Maybe you've heard a new name?
Berdugo.
Berdugo?
I just heard that name today.
Someone here is asking
about Berdugo.
That's our boss's name,
isn't it, Sir?
Find out who's asking
about Berdugo.
My child Joey,
are you back at the dorm yet?
You didn't update me.
I was tired last night.
I fell asleep.
That's why you and Peter
haven't seen each other, right?
Peter?
Hello, Peter?
Joey, I'm glad I talked to you.
Where are you?
Andrew and I are following
a lead.
There's this woman
under my radar.
It's Delilah.
She's the one suspected
of being in charge of drug
distribution here in Valmora.
You know, if Berdugo will meet
someone here, it might be her.
That's good.
She owns several businesses
here in Valmora.
One of them is the new
Nature Hotel and Resort.
Okay, I'll check in there
to investigate.
Just stay put.
I'll take care of it.
Boss Delilah, I'll return
your money right away.
I'll find a way!
You should have done
that a long time ago.
- I'm sorry.
- Boss, don't.
So what? Are we really
at a dead end here?
Has "Joey On Duty" lost her
courage?l
But what are we going to do?
Actually,
I've thought of something.
I just don't know
if you'll agree.
Okay, I'm game.
What are you doinlg here?
Boss Idol!
Hi.
I called earlier for a suite.
Hold on...
Here's my card.
Wow. You're something else.
You even booked a couple's room.
Of course, only the best
for my girlfriend.
You're in trouble,
your ex seems affected.
I'll explain to her
when I get the chance.
That's our only way to be near
the subject.
Boss Idol...
- I mean, Mr. Dizon.
- Yes?
Here's your card and key.
I got you the best room
for couples, Sir.
Thank you.
By the way,
how's the security here?
You're safe here, Boss Idol.
We have CCTVs.
Even though there's no guard,
they're recording 24/7.
But don't worry, Boss Idol.
The people here are nice.
Like you, right?
You're very nice.
Yes.
Anyway, okay, thank you.
Let's check the couple's room?
Francis.
Clean that up.
Yes, Madam.
Aren't you used to it by now?
We've been doing that
for a long time.
Send a big suitcase here
to Madam's room.
Please hurry.
Copy.
Thank you.
Why do you look pale?
Remember, this is what we do.
So you just have to get used
to it,
especially from those who take
advantage of us.
What were you thinking?
Didn't I tell you...
Zoey, didn't I tell you
to be quiet?
There's a CCTV camera there.
Didn't I tell you to stay home?
My mission might be jeopardized.
Look. We won't be in your way.
Do your mission,
and Joey and I will do
our strategy.
What, for you to flirt with your
girlfriend while I do the job?
We have our own investigation,
and the only way to keep people
from suspecting me,
even if they see me,
is to show them that I am
on vacation, okay?
You know, whatever you're
planning,
don't continue with it.
Get out of here now.
If this is what I need to do
to help my father,
to find him, I will do it.
You can't get me out of here.
If you want, arrest me.
Just make sure you don't ruin
my plan.
Okay.
How long will it take?
It's been a few days.
To this day, we still haven't
seen my husband's remains.
To be honest,
even I am getting frustrated.
I know this is hard
for your family,
but we have to follow the
protocol of the investigation.
Chief, damn those protocols!
My husband has been burned,
and yet you won't leave him
in peace!
I'm really sorry, Mrs. Delgado.
Clarissa, but all I can do
is follow up and wait.
And how long are we going
to wait?
My daughter's mind
is going through something
because she hasn't seen
Miguel yet.
Chief, she feels like Miguel
is still alive.
Chief, I'm begging you,
show me Miguel.
Then let's do your protocols
later on.
Thank you.
Thank you, Chief.
I'll find a way, Clarissa.
Your husband is a good man
and a good cop,
and he doesn't deserve this.
That's why I'm begging you.
Just be patient.
Okay, Chief.
It's just really hard
because there's no closure
to what happened to Miguel.
Don't worry.
I'll call you once
he's released.
I promise...
I'll get Miguel back to you
as soon as possible.
Thank you.
Cruz, please take her
to the door.
Sir, the package has been
delivered to Delgado.
I hope it helps
with his mission.
I wonder who owns this.
Black sedan,
ELS 8-0-2-5.
Peter, why did you call me?
Here.
I'm returning these to you.
What?
I gave these to you.
I don't need it anymore.
Why?
I talked to Joey.
She's with Andrew.
I even got worried.
They say they're following
a lead.
What lead?
Is this about the syndicate?
I don't know. I didn't ask.
Joey was in a hurry.
Are you okay?
No matter what makeover I do,
it's useless.
I still lose to Andrew.
He can help Joey better
in his situation than I can.
While here I am...
Useless.
Madam Delilah,
I'll take care of this!
Okay!
There's this woman under
my radar, it's Delilah.
She's the one suspected
of being in charge
of drug distribution here
in Valmora.
You know, if Berdugo will meet
someone here, it might be her.
Hello, good morning!
Good morning.
Excuse me.
Confirmed,
Delilah is here.
Exactly, and right next
to our villa,
which means we can more easily
monitor her every move.
At least, we'll know if she's
really meeting with Berdugo.
We'll take our time
before we investigate.
But for now, stay here
until she makes a move.
Let's check the villa.
We probably don't need
to pretend all the way inside,
right?
Of course.
Joey, don't feel awkward
with me.
That's the last thing
I want you to feel.
- I'll just sleep on the sofa.
- No, no...
I'll be on the sofa.
You can have the bed.
That's great.
And the CR, let's schedule it.
Can I just go first
in the morning?
In the morning?
What about...
What about if there's
an emergency?
If you can't take it anymore,
your stomach hurts?
Well, you can do it outside.
You can handle that. You're old.
Wow. Wow, okay.
Anyway, I'll just get our stuff
in the car.
Joey, let's stick to the plan.
And whatever happens to us
here while pretending,
I want you to know
that I will protect you.
I'll go ahead.
Let's just follow Joey
and Andrew.
We can help them too.
And that way, you will have
a chance with Joey.
No need.
I'll just look desperate
and need attention.
Instead of getting closer
to her,
I'll just keep my distance
so I can forget!
I'll just go back
to the province.
Are you leaving?
Why?
Will you miss me?
No.
I'll miss you.
You're the only true friend
I've ever had here.
Thank you.
Thank you for all your kindness.
Someday, I will return
the favor.
Thank you for being
a good friend.
I'm not because I wasn't
completely honest with you.
You're talking to me
in Korean again.
What did you say?
I said I will miss the guy who
keeps calling me Oppa.
Things will get better.
Trust me. Just be careful, okay?
Yeah, Oppa.
Zoey!
Zoey, wait a minute.
What are you doing?
Someone might see us here.
Just relax.
I'm also a hotel guest.
I don't think
there's something wrong
with talking to another guest?
What do you want?
I want to apologize.
For not listening to me?
Yes,
and if it's any help,
we've confirmed that Delilah
is here.
She's just in the room next
to ours.
And?
That's it?
Yeah.
I'll just give you some more
info once I get something.
And I know you didn't like
what I did.
And I feel like we'll get better
results if we work together,
Zoey.
Is it okay for your girlfriend
to share?
We're just pretending.
And I feel like she won't mind
if we share info.
The guy in red,
we saw in the other room.
He called Delilah, Boss.
You're my ticket to getting
closer to Delilah.
Get everything...
Clarissa...
what are you doing here?
Ma'am, because I have
some work left to do.
I thought it would be better
to finish it first.
Clarissa, I know what happened
to your husband.
My condolences.
How are you doing?
It's okay, Ma'am.
I'm trying to be busy.
You don't have to do that.
I've assigned someone to do
your work.
I know how hard
what you've been going through.
Is that so, Ma'am?
Well, sorry,
sorry for the hassle, but...
Ma'am, it's better this way
than having to worry about
when my husband's body
will be released.
And besides, what my daughter
said is also right.
She said
"Life should just go on."
I understand,
but I got you covered here,
okay?
I'll understand if you can't
come to the foundation for now.
Me too,
I might not be able to take care
of my foundation for now.
Why, Ma'am?
Well, Mom lost her caregiver,
so I'll take care of her
for now.
It's hard to find a replacement.
Well Ma'am,
if you can't find one,
I'm available.
No. It's embarrassing.
Go ahead, Ma'am.
Please agree.
I need this.
It's also a way to get rid of
the sadness in my mind.
If you agree, I'm not the only
one helping you.
You can help me too.
Just put it on the table.
Thank you.
Hello there!
Hello.
I didn't know I had a neighbor.
I'm Madam Delilah.
Joey.
Let me guess.
Room service?
You must be alone.
No.
Actually, I'm with my boyfriend.
We just got here, so I ordered
room service first.
That's not acceptable.
You know what,
you should enjoy this place!
You know,
we have camping areas here
where you can enjoy dinner
under the stars.
Don't worry,
I'll have that ready.
Okay, okay. It's embarrassing.
Besides, we don't have
any equipment because...
No, no, no, no.
Don't think about that
because I believe being in love
should always be celebrated
and treasured.
Call Francis for their camping
needs.
You know, it's a shame.
I have an appointment later,
but if I catch up with you
tonight,
I hope you don't mind sharing
your story of how you met.
Sure, okay. Thank you.
You're welcome, my dear.
I'll see you later, I hope.
- See you later.
- Okay.
So, you're Delilah.
Why did he leave
his cell phone here?
He's such a jerk.
Where did you come from?
What took you so long?
Why would you leave
your cell phone here?
You're too much...
and I'm coming back.
Exaggerated.
Why? Is there a problem?
Delilah left.
She left?
Well then, let's follow her.
Do you know where she went?
No, I don't know.
But I heard she'll be back
tonight.
Then I guess there's nothing we
can do.
There is.
There's no one in the villa.
We can go in,
maybe we can get a clue.
You take care of our shipments.
Make sure the quality
of our products.
It's okay, Boss,
same as before.
Tell our staff to pick me up
from home on the way to Valmora.
Matias,
why aren't you answering?
Boss, maybe I should just go
to Valmora?
Why?
Castro, our contact in
the police department,
said that someone asked
about Berdugo.
Boss, maybe they're suspecting.
So there won't be any problem,
I'll meet with Delilah.
Hurry up.
Just wait.
Have you eaten yet?
Where do you want to eat first?
- I want Japanese.
- Japanese?
There's no Japanese here.
- I'll have my nails done.
- That's great.
Can you open that?
Of course.
Watch and learn.
I'll take care of you.
You're all on standby here?
I want you all to welcome
my special guest
when he arrives.
Yes, Madam Delilah.
Dear...
I knew it.
I forgot something in my safe.
Hello?
- I'm done cleaning! Come on...
- Come...
What are you doing?
Just trust me, okay?
We should be sticking
to our characters
so no one will catch us.
Is the person you're talking
to trustworthy, Madam Delilah?
When will we meet
the new supplier?
I'll be leaving Manila soon.
I'll be there and continue
with our plan.
Don't worry about anything.
Nothing will go wrong here.
- Ouch.
- Are you okay?
No, I'm not!
Stay here. Wait for me.
- I'll just look for clues.
- Are you leaving me here?
Joey, there's a safe [box] here.
Do you know the combination
code?
Why are you standing outside
my room?
Check everywhere! Check inside.
Maybe it was just the wind
earlier?
You look scared.